Guide to the John W. Shenk Papers, 1900-1935
Department of Special Collections
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - R - GENERAL IN. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ricca, Vetran.
      See American Legion.
    - Richards, John E., '26-'27
    - Richards, Mary W., '31
    - Richards, R. D., '20
    - Richardson, Bonner., '27; (2)
    - RICHARDSON, FRIEND WILLIAM (1865 -)., '24-'25; (3) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Riddle, Lester C., '29-'31; (3)
    - Ridgway, J. L., '23; (3)
    - RIDGWAY, THOMAS C., '26-'34; (11) (Box 7, Folder 5)
      See also AMERICAN LAW INSTITUTE.
    - Riegler, Gordon A., '22
    - Rietzke, E., '24
    - Riley, James Sheldon (1879 -)., '24
    - Ringer, Elva F., '24
    - Ringo, Richard G., '31
    - Rio Antiguo Mining Company., '08
    - Rivers, J. A.
    - Roberts, Caesar A., '25-'31; (3)
    - Roberts, Frederick M., '31
    - Roberts, Roy Ray., '25
    - Roberts, Walter Adolph (1886 -)., '13
    - Robinson, Dudley., '23-'33
    - Robinson, Jane Bancroft., '23-24; (3)
    - Robinson, Leonard George (1875 -)., '28; (2)
    - Robinson, Stephen Bernard., '08-'31; (4)
    - Robinson, Thomas W., '24
    - Robinson, William L., '32
    - Robson, Kernan., '28; (2)
    - Rochester, George W., '27-'33; (6)
    - Rockafellor, J. E., '24
    - Rodgers, J. E., '34
    - Roller, P. F., '27-'30; (2)
    - Rolph Memorial Fund., '34
    - Roosevelt Camp, U.S.W.V., '24
    - Roosevelt Club Of Southern California., '23; (2)
    - Roosevelt Progressive Republican League., '12
    - Root, Elihu (1845 -).
    - Rose, Henry Howard (1856 -)., '13
    - Rosecrans, William Starke (1889 -)., '20
    - Rosenkranz, Elias V., '25-'29; (3)
    - Ross, J. Stewart., '27
    - Roth, Lester William (1895 -)., '24
    - Rothacker-Allen Laboratories, Inc., '22
    - Routhe, A. C., '14-'24
    - Rowell, Chester Harvey (1867 -)., '14
    - The Roycrafters., '26
    - Rubin, I. R., '30
    - Rubin, Samuel., '26
    - Rule, J. H., '13
    - Ruling Case Law., '30
    - Ruoff, Hermann F., '21-'25; (3)
    - Rushton, George M., '13
    - Russill, Louis P., '24
    - Rutherford, Nathaniel R., '24
    - A. J. Rutledge & Sons., '24-'26; (5)
    - Rutledge, Frank B., '25
  - S - GENERAL IN (I). (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Sabel, Henry.
    - Sacramento Bar Association.
    - Sacramento Bee., '32
    - Sacramento Veteran., '31
    - Sadicoff, Harry G., '27
    - Saint Ignatius Club., '14
    - Saint Ignatius College., '30
    - St. Odilia's., '26-'27
    - St. Patrick's Rectory., '14
    - Salvation Army., '20-'24; (3)
    - Sample, Ed. P., '23
    - Sampsel, Lloyd E., '23-'26; (3)
    - San Diego Bar Association.
    - San Francisco. City and County. Board Of Supervisors., '30-'33; (3)
    - San Francisco Advertising Club., '32
    - San Francisco Bar Association., nd, '28; (3)
    - San Francisco Bay Toll-Bridge Company., '29
    - San Francisco Bulletin., '28
    - San Francisco Chronicle., '25-'27
    - San Francisco Convention Executive Committee., '26
    - San Francisco Down Town Association., '24
    - San Francisco Examiner., '26
    - San Gabriel Cemetery Association., '28
    - San Gabriel Valley Country Club., '06-'20; (17)
    - San Joaquin Light and Power Corporation., '22
    - Sanaker, Otto., '25
    - Sandborn, Mrs. A. R., '27
    - Sanford, J. W., '20
    - Santa Clara, University Of., '31; (4)
    - Santa Monica Bay Chapter, No. 97., '22
    - Sargent, John Garibaldi (1860 -)., '27
    - Satterwhite, J. W., '27
    - Schauer, Benjamin Rey (1891 -)., '27-'34
    - Scheinman, B. J., '27; (2)
    - Schmidt, Ruben S., '24
    - Schultz, Carl., '13-'14
    - Schulz, Edward F., '24-'31; (5)
    - Schmittou, C. V., '30
    - Schrader. Frederick von., '32; (2)
    - Schweitzer, Dell A., '26-'33; (3)
    - Scofield, Jerome V., '29
    - Score, J. N. R., '25
    - Scott, Joseph (1867 -)., '24-'28
    - Scott, Robert H., '26; (2)
    - Scott, S. C., '24
    - Scott, W. E.
    - Scripps College., '28
    - Seager, Howard W., '24-'29
    - Sears, Charles W., '27
    - Seawell, Emmet James (1907 -)., '34
    - Security First National Bank Of Los Angeles., '22-'35; (55) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Seiter, Orville R., '29
    - Self-Governing Bar, Special Committee On., '25
    - Selleck, Wesley T., '22
    - Senior, George T., '09
    - Seymour, Joseph F., '24-'34
    - SHANK, EDMOND. (brother of J.W. Shenk), nd, '07-'35; (86) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sharkey, Will R., '24
    - Shaw, Charles H., '30
    - Shaw, Hartley (1874 -)., '08-'33; (3)
    - Shaw, John C., '31
    - Shaw, Joseph E., '33
    - Shaw, Lucien (1845 -)., '15-'29; (3)
    - Shaw, Victor E., nd, '24; (2)
    - Shaw, Warwick A., '07; (3)
    - Shelby, Mrs. J., '23
    - Sheldon, Charles H., '31
    - Shelley, L. M., '32; (2)
    - Shelly, Mrs. Charles H., nd, '22; (2)
    - SHENK, ADOLPHUS M. (brother of J.W. Shenk)., nd, '96-'35; (160) (Box 8, Folder 2)
      See also McEverlast, Inc.
    - SHENK, JOHN WESLEY (18 - 1921) (father of J.W. Shenk)., nd, '03-'21; (70) (Box 8, Folder 3)
      See also SHENK PROPERTY.
    - SHENK, JOHN WESLEY (1875 - 19), including letters to the following persons:
      - Unidentified., (6) (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - - A - (Box 8, Folder 5)
          - Abbott, William M., '30
          - Abel, Edson C., '22
          - Ace Sheet Metal Works., '29
          - Adams, Ida May., '23
          - Addleman, Joseph A., '35
          - Aetna Life Insurance Co., '29
          - Aggeler, William Tell., '27-'31; (2)
          - Agnew, H. M., '26
          - Alameda County Bar Association.
            See Bar Associations.
          - Alberti, Robert A., '24
          - Alco, Julian H., '30
          - Alderson, William A., '30; (2)
          - Alfonso, Herbert D., '25
          - Alhambra, City Of. Board Of Trustees., '13
          - Allan, Robert N., '20
          - Allen, Alfred W., '13
          - Allen, Carroll., '25
          - Allen, E. R., '13
          - Allender Frank., '13; (2)
          - Amador Valley Savings Bank., '27-'32; (5)
          - American Bar Association.
          - American Bar Association Journal., '24
          - American Historical Society., '19
          - American Judicature Society., '33
          - American Law Book Company., '24
          - American Law Institute., '27; (2)
          - American Legion., '30-'32; (2)
          - American Trust Company., '28
          - Ames, E. Neal., '30
          - Anderson, George W., '27-'28
          - Anderson, James A., '24
          - Anderson, William H., nd, '25-'27; (3)
          - Andreani, Frank M., '22-'28
          - Andrews, Alexander B., '27
          - Angellotti, Frank M., '27
          - Antelope Valley News., '24
          - Arizona Supreme Court., '34
          - Arizona, University of., '29
          - Armond, Phillip., '31
          - Atherton, A. W., '13
          - Ault, D. L., '24
          - Austin, Robert E., '27
          - Automobile Club Of Southern California., '25
          - Avery, Russ., '24; (3)
          - Ayres, Albert D., '29
        - - B - (Box 8, Folder 6)
          - Babson Institute., '32
          - Backus, J. J., '11
          - Bailie, Norman A., '24-'30
          - Baird, William S., '26-'32; (3)
          - Baker, Sheridan W., '25-'29
          - BANK OF AMERICA., '24-'34; (20) (Box 8, Folder 7)
          - Bank Of California., '30
          - Bannister, E. W., '13
          - Bantzer, Edward H., '20
          - BAR ASSOCIATIONS., '27-'35; (29) (Box 8, Folder 8)
          - Barclay, D. Eric., '24
          - Barham, Frank Forrest., '28
          - Barnes, Frank T., '28
          - Barnett, Ray E., '20
          - Barnhill, William A., '24
          - Barry, R. W., '24
          - Bartoo, Mrs. E., '24
          - Bass, Mrs. C. A. Spear., '34
          - Bassett, Wilbur., '27
          - Batcheller, Charles L., '13
          - Bayne, Pierre Curran., '28
          - Baze, Ross B., '25
          - Bearman, William W., '20
          - Beatson, J. W., '27
          - Bechtel, W. A. Jr., '35
          - Becker, Tracy Chatfield., '32-'33; (2)
          - Beirne, William B., '31
          - Bell Chesterfield Bed Company., '30
          - Bender, H. W., '25
          - Benedict, H. Stanley., '13
          - Benjamin, M. J., '32
          - Bennett, Mrs. Earl D., '33
          - Bent, Charles E., '33-'35; (3)
          - Berkebile, Thomas A., '24
          - Bernstein, D. Brandon., '34
          - Berry, Leon F., '26
          - Beta Theta Pi., '26-'30
          - Betkeuski, Martin F., '27
          - Bettencourt, Joe., '26
          - Beutel, Frederick., '24; (2)
          - Biby, John E., '13-'26
          - Billig, Clinton A., '13-'35
          - Biscailuz, Eugene W., '34
          - Bishop, Edward T., '35
          - Bitler, Don C., '24
          - Blair, Isidor D., '31
          - Blanks, A. F., '24-'25; (3)
          - Blight, Reynold E., '13-'16; (5)
          - Bliss, Charles H. J., '28
          - Blockley, Edward., '29
          - Bobbs-Merrill Company., '07
          - Bodley, Thomas.
            See Santa Clara Co. Tax Collector.
          - Boone, Thomas C., '33
          - Booth, Morton., '32
          - Booth, Vincent Ravi., '31
          - Booth, Willis H., '13
          - Borden, Sheldon., '24
          - Bordwell Mathews and Wardsworth., '32
          - Boucher, E. S., '20
          - Boys' Day In Citizenship., '34
          - Bragonier, George W., '26
          - Bresee Brothers., '28-'35
          - Brickley, Michael J., '34
          - Britsch, Frank W., '25; (2)
          - Britt, E. W., '13
          - Brooks, Frances G., '29
          - Brooks, R. A., '13
          - Brown, Luther G., '25-'26; (3)
          - Brown, Thomas P., '34
          - Browne Roofing Company., '28; (2)
          - Bryant, W. Byron., '35
          - Bryson, Charles W., '24
          - Budd, Charles., '26
          - Budd, Claya A., '29
          - Buehler, Harold M., '28
          - Bulkley, Olcott S., '30
          - Bundy, Carl A., '22-'30
          - Burke, John C., '33
          - Burke, John P., nd
          - Burke, Thomas F., '30
          - Burke, W. Maxwell., '24-'26; (3)
          - Burlingame Country Club., '24; (2)
          - Burnett, C. H., '27
          - Burton, John F., '25
          - Bush, David W., '24
          - Bush, George B.
            See Lincoln Club.
          - Bush, George C., '26-'27
          - Bush, Samuel T., '27
          - Bush and Clyburn.
            See IRELAND, ESTATE OF.
          - Butcher, C. H., '27
          - Buttle, W. F., '27
          - Button, A. Ronald., '31
          - Buzzell, J. W.
            See Los Angeles Central Labor Council.
          - Byers, Essie., '24
        - - C - (Box 8, Folder 9)
          - Calexico National Bank., '11-'30; (3)
          - California Blue Book., '28
          - California, State Of.
            - Board Of Parole and Pardons., '20; (2)
            - Board Of Prison Directors., '22-'30; (14)
            - Controller., nd, '33-'34; (3)
            - Corporation Department., '22
            - Department Of Investment. Division Of Real Estate., '32
            - Division Of Motor Vehicles., '22
            - State Prison at San Quentin. Warden., '23
            - Secretary of State, Deputy., '30; (2)
            - Treasurer., '33
            - University Of., '29
          - California State Bar Association.
          - Calkins, John U. Jr., '32
          - Calvert, J. W. Jr., '20
          - Campbell, Kemper., '25-'29
          - Campbell, Mrs. Kemper., '29-'32; (6)
          - Cammert, E. T., '28
          - Card, M. B., nd
          - Carleton, Frank E., '32
          - Carlin, Keith., '27
          - Carlson, Arthur J., '26
          - Carnes, Charles Newell., '20
          - Carpenter, Walter C., '23
          - Carr, P. E., '16
          - Carr, William J., '27
          - Carter, Henry E., '23-'27
          - CARTER, JESSE W., '24-'35; (11) (Box 8, Folder 10)
          - Cary, W. P., '22
          - Cass, A. B., '20
          - Castle, J. Jay., '33
          - Castle Rock Oil Company., '23
          - Cato, M. Raymond., '32
          - Caukin, Mrs. Grace B., '23-'27
          - Central Christian Advocate., '29
          - Chaffey, Andrew M., '26
          - Challberg, C. E., '26
          - CHAMBERLIN, HARRY A., '23-'30; (15) (Box 8, Folder 11)
          - Chambers, Joseph F., '27
          - Chandler, Charles L., '24
          - Chandler, Harry., '25-'34; (3)
          - Chase, Lucius K., '30
          - Chase, Ralph A., '13
          - Chenoweth, Orr M., '30
          - Chesebro, Ray L., '33-'34
          - Chipman, Ida E., '24
          - Chisam, C. J., '24
          - Christian Endeavorers., '13
          - Church, Percy Clarke., '26; (3)
          - Clarke, Lucian J., '31
          - Clarke, Robert M., '29-'33
          - Clarke, Thurmond., '29-'32; (5)
          - Clarkson, James H. B., '22
          - Clear Lake Lodge., '26
          - Cleary, Alfred J., '32
          - Clock, Ralph H., '24
          - Close, W. H.
            See Preston School Of Industry.
          - Cochran, George I., '26
          - Cockrell, Ewing., '28
          - Cohen, Benjamin C., '26-'33; (3)
          - Cohen, Herbert., '27-'31
          - Cole, Louis M., '22-'26; (6)
          - Coleman, B. H., '25
          - COLLIER, FRANK C., '25-'31; (15) (Box 8, Folder 12)
          - P. F. Collier and Son., '31
          - Collings, Lewis D., '26
          - Colvin, Will., '24
          - Conley, W. M., '30
          - Connor, James., '27; (3)
          - Conrad, Edna P., '19
          - CONREY, NATHANIEL P., '23-'32; (5) (Box 8, Folder 13)
          - Cook and Nichols., '24
          - Cook, Stanko., '22
          - Cook, W. J., '22
          - Cooley, C. P., '28
          - Cooper, C. V., '32
          - Cooper, John S., '27
          - Copp, Andrew J., '23-'31; (4)
          - Copper, Charles A., '25
          - Corbell, Louis M., '27
          - Cosgrave, George., '30
          - Coshow, Oliver P., '28
          - Couch, J. P., '23
          - Council, C. B., '30
          - Council, William H., '24-'28; (5)
          - Coutts, John M., '30-'34
          - Craft, Kenneth S., '22
          - Craig, J. C., '24
          - Craig, William T., '27
          - Crail, Charles S., '28-'31; (3)
          - Crail, Joseph., '31
          - Crane, A. Bathurst., '25
          - Crane, C. C., '25
          - Cranston, John., '32
          - Crawford, John H., '31
          - Crawford, Samuel J., '30
          - Cremin, J. M., '25
          - Crippin, Paul A., '22
          - Cropley, Maria., '10
          - Crow, S. E., '22
          - Cryer, George E., '23-'28
          - CRUMP, GUY RICHARDS., '24-'29; (9) (Box 8, Folder 14)
            See also IRELAND, ESTATE OF.
          - Cruzan, Ide., '31
          - Culver, Robert J. O., '24-'32; (6)
          - Cumming, Joseph M., '24
          - Cummings, Homer S., '33-'35
          - Curtin, John T., nd, '26; (3)
          - Curtis, Jesse W., '24-'31; (4)
          - Custer, Charles R., '25-'30; (5)
        - - D - (Box 9, Folder 1)
          - Daily News., '28; (2)
          - Dam, F. H., '33
          - Daney, Eugene., '30
          - danielson, Carl A., '23; (2)
          - Dartmouth College., '29
          - Daugherty, Richard B.
            See Stanford University.
          - [Davidson, Adolph T.]
            See Los Angeles, Co. Sheriff.
          - DeBower, Edward W., '35
          - DeGarmo, B. W.
            see California, State of. Department Of Investment.
          - DeGarmo, G. Curtis., '23-'27
          - DeLaMonte, J. H., '13
          - Denby, Edwin., '23
          - Dennett, L. L., '27; (2)
          - Dennis, Albert E., '22
          - Desmond, Walter J., '34
          - Dillon, John., '26
          - Dillon, Richard J., '11
          - Dinkelspiel, Henry G. W., '29
          - Docker, Frederick W., '29
          - Dockweiler, Isidore B., '31
          - Dodge, Jonathan S., '22-'32
          - Dodson, George R., '25-'26
          - Dodson, Philip F., '24
          - Doherty, Frank P., '13
          - Dollar, Harold., '34
          - Dollar Steamship Lines, Inc., '32
          - Donavin, George B., '23
          - Donohoe, Nellie G., '33
          - Donohugh, W. L., '20; (2)
          - Doran, W. C., '32
          - Dortin and Burnett., '22
          - Dougherty, Paul B.
            See JUDICIAL COUNCIL.
          - Dove, F. Roy., '24-'25; (3)
          - Dove, T. C., '27
          - Drake, Frank., '24
          - Drake, Marjory H., '27
          - Dreifus, Charles., '24
          - Dryer, George W., '24
          - Dunker, Minnie E., '28-'31
          - Dunlavy, Melvin T., '31
          - Dunnigan, J. S., '30
          - Dunniway, Ben C., '31
          - Dutton, C. C. S., '30
          - Dyer, Frederick R., nd, '30; (2)
          - Dyke, Harry N., '32
        - - E - (Box 9, Folder 2)
          - Easton, William E., '27
          - Eaton, Fred., '27; (3)
          - Eddy, Elfored., '24; (2)
          - Edmonds, Douglas L., '25-'33
          - Edwards, D. K., '13
          - Edwards, David W., '23
          - Edwards, LeRoy M., '29
          - Ehlert, William., '25
          - Ehnes, Morris W., '24
          - El Centro, California. County Tax Collector., '08; (2)
          - Eldridge, F. W., '22
          - ELKS, BENEVOLENT PROTECTIVE ORDER OF., '27-'32; (3) (Box 9, Folder 3)
          - Elks Magazine., '24
          - Elliott, John B., '24-'34
          - Elwell, J. F., '35
          - Emerson, Richard S., '25
          - Emme, Otto J., '23
          - Emmons, C. H., '24-'25
          - Encyclopedia Brittanica, Inc., '28
          - Entenza, Antonio P., nd
          - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States., '23-'31; (5)
          - John M. Eshleman Memorial Association., '29
          - Estes, Frank., '29
          - Eubank, C. H., '20
          - Evans, William E., '28
          - Eversole, Keith C., '24-'35; (13)
          - Eyton, Charles., '20
        - - F - (Box 9, Folder 4)
          - Fairfax Volunteer Fire Department., '25
          - Faries, David R., '22-30; (6)
          - Farley, James A., '33; (2)
          - Farrand, George E., '31-'34
          - Federal Building and Loan Association., '28
          - Federal Emergency Administration Of Public Works., '33
          - Federal Land Bank Of Berkeley., '25; (2)
          - Fidelity Union Title and Mortgage Guarantee Company., '26
          - Finch, William M., '23-'31; (3)
          - FINLAYSON, FRANCIS., '23-'27; (12) (Box 9, Folder 5)
          - First National Bank Of Los Angeles., '11-'25; (7)
          - First National Bank. Pleasanton, Calif., '30
          - Fitch, H. G., '24
          - Fitts, Buron., '26
          - fitzgerald, Fred J., '25
          - Flaherty, Hugh F., '26
          - Flannery, Mrs. D. J.
            See San Jose, California.
          - Fleming, John L., '29-'31
          - Fletcher, Kimball., '26
          - Flint, Motley H., '11; (2)
          - Florez, Angelo.
            See Gannon, Thomas M.
          - fong, Lester V., '24
          - Foote, D. A., '16
          - Foreign Service Magazine., '25
          - Forest Lawn Memorial Park Association., '22-'31; (5)
          - Forrester, C. Henry., '23
          - Foster, Mrs. Laura., '25
          - Fox, W. Turney., '31-'32
          - Frankum, Mrs. Anna M., '24
          - Frazier, Henry A., '22; (2)
          - Fredericks, John D., '23-'24; (3)
          - Fredin, E. P., '26
          - Freeman, G. R., '30
          - Fricke, Charles W., '22-'28; (3)
          - Fulcher, Charles E. R., '24-'26; (4)
          - Fuller, G. H., '24
          - Fulton and Fulton., '29
        - - G - (Box 9, Folder 6)
          - Galen, Albert J., '25
          - Galley, Elizabeth., '24
          - Galusha, Elon G., '34
          - Gannon, Thomas M., '26
          - Gant, Valentine., '08
          - Garrison, Carrie., '13
          - Garrison, Walter E., '32
          - Garstin, Mrs. Herbert H., '29
          - Gates, Don S., '20
          - Gates, Lee C.
            See Roosevelt Progressive Republican League.
          - Geer, Margaret., '27
          - Geer, Richard L., '25-'30
          - Geissler, Edward A., '25
          - Gerecht, E. F., '23
          - Gibbs, Elliott., '22
          - Gibbs, G. A., '20-'24
          - Gibson, Lilburn., '27; (2)
          - Gifford, Harry N., '08-'30; (5)
          - Gilbert, William H., '25
          - Gilbreath, J. W., '13
          - Gillett, J. N., '08
          - Ginty, John., '25
          - Gist, J. B., '24
          - Globe Petroleum Company., '25-'28
          - Godfrey, Marcus L., '30-'33
          - Godfrey, Marcus L. Jr., '33
          - Goff, Roy., '24
          - Goldberg, Bowen and Co., '29
          - Goldschmidt, Herman H., '24-'35; (14)
          - Goodcell, Rex B., '31
          - Goodell, C. Julian., '28-'29
          - Goodwin, Vernon., '31
          - Gordon, G. B., '22; (2)
          - Gordon, Hugh., '25-'27; (3)
          - Goree, L. J. Jr., '30; (2)
          - Gould, Thomas C., '24-'27
          - Graham, Harry., '27
          - Graney, Donald C., '33; (2)
          - Grant, '24
          - Granville, Mrs. Sylvia M., '22
          - Gray, J. Walter., '26
          - Gray, Mrs. L. M., '29
          - Graydon, Mrs. Betty M., '31
          - Green, Dan W., '24-'35; (6)
          - Green, J. B., '24; (2)
          - Greenstock, Commander and Mrs. Arthur., '29-'31
          - Grismore, Grover C., '27
          - Grua, E. T., '27
          - Guerin, C. Walter., '24
          - Guernsey, P. B., '31
          - Gurley, Boyd., '28
        - - H - (Box 9, Folder 7)
          - Haas, Charles E., '24-'29; (5)
          - Haas, Walter F., '35
          - Haber, Michael., '28
          - Hahn, Benjamin., '26-'27; (3)
          - Hahn, S. S., '30
          - Halbert, Sherrill., '26
          - Hall, Wilbur., '27
          - Hamilton, Mrs. G. A., '07
          - Hamilton, John J., '13
          - Hamilton, William B., '31
          - Hammer, Fred H., '20-'24
          - Hampton and Smallwood., '30
          - Hance, C. H., '10
          - Handley, Lorin A., '13
          - Handy, Thomas B., '07
          - Hanley, Robert L., '26-'27
          - Hanlon, William J., '33
          - Hanna, Byron C., '27
          - Hanna, Sam C., '32
          - Harris, George B., '08-'26; (5)
          - Harris, Lamar A., '07
          - Harrison, Maurice E., '34-'35
          - Harter, Mrs. Noble., '26
          - Hartman, Louis O., '29
          - Hartzell, Mrs. Florence., '31
          - Hastings, Hills., '25
          - Hatch, Percy B., '23
          - Hatfield, George J., '33-'35
          - Hatheway, David Gilbert., '27
          - Hatteroth, W. H., '26
          - Haverty, Thomas., '20-'24
          - Hawkins, J. W., '24
          - Hawley, J. O., '13
          - Heales, Carl LeRoy., '22
          - Heaney, Price and Postel., '32
          - Heffley, George R., '24
          - Hegardt, G. B.
            See Oakland, Port of.
          - Hellman, Marco H., '27
          - Hellman Commercial Trust and Savings Bank., '23
          - Helms, G. S., '08
          - Helser, Charles W., '25
          - Henderson, Frank G., '29
          - Henderson, George A., '25-'26; (3)
          - Hermosa Beach, California. City Clerk., '23
          - Herrick, Anson., '27
          - Herrick, C. A., '22
          - Hettman, Walter E., '33
          - Hewitt, Asa., '30
          - Hewitt, Emily Ellen., '28
          - Hewitt, Leslie R., '08-'33; (14)
          - Hibbard, Oley., '30
          - Hickcox, Ross T., '24-'34; (4)
          - Hicks, John J., '13
          - Hill, A. G., '33
          - Hill, A. J., '26-'33; (4)
          - Hill, John J., '25-'27
          - Hill, Robert G., '23
          - Hiss, Bernard G., '31
          - Hjelm, Gustav B., nd, '20; (3)
          - Hobday, R. D., '24-'25; (3)
          - Hodel, George., '24; (2)
          - Hodghead, Beverly L., '24
          - Hoefner, Edward W., '27